next hit time is affected by having to
access the tlb before we access the
cache remember that the processor starts
out with a virtual address we use some
part of that virtual address to index
into the tlb and find the frame number
we then combine that with the page
offset and now that we have the physical
address we can use it to access our
cache and get the data from it so really
if the tlb takes one cycle and the cache
takes one cycle we need two cycles from
when the processor gives us the address
until we actually get the data because
really the tlb access and the cash
access have to happen one after the
other a cash that is accessed using a
physical address is called a physically
accessed cache a physical cache and also
it is called physically indexed or
physically tagged or P PT
cash the overall hit latency of that
cash really is the tlb hit latency and
the cash heat latency